敷かれたレール
素直に進めば
目隠ししても
どこかに行き着く
でも人生は緋い誘惑の糸に
操られて
囚われるがままに
Days flying by
but still wonder why
I look to the sky and cry
So lost inside
There's no place to hide
A prisoner to pride
LAST TRIGGER
Save me
世界の果てで
ただ独り残されて
引き金にかかった指が震えた
運命のスコープを覗いて
未来が変わるのなら
心信じて
狙い定めて
幼い記憶に残された
静寂な日々を
いつか失ってしまうことばかり恐れ
どんなに足掻いたとしても
答えを知っても
崩れる
EPITOME
現実の荒波に心の声奪われそうで
I can't comprehend
The noise in my head
This nightmare will never end
The look in your eyes
The fire burns alive
A new hope will rise
Save me
世界の果てで
ただ光追いかけて
手探りで掴んだ夢が輝いた
モノクロームを超えて
自分が変わるのなら
瞳閉じて
闇仕留めて
Don't hesitate
もしもこの体
明日消えるなら
あなたと見上げる夜空を
この目に焼き付けたくて
もしもこの声が
いつか届くのなら
枯れるまでその名を叫んで
I'll bring you back from a
世界の果てで
ただ独り残されて
引き金にかかった指が震えた
運命のスコープを覗いて
未来が変わるのなら
The future is yours to own
Your heart will lead you on
あなたを信じて
狙い定めて
Bull's eye
First impact
will break me
Last trigger
will take me
First impact
will break me
Last trigger
will take me